(Penny:)So, Bernadette, how goes the hunt
for bridesmaid dresses?
(Bernadette:)Well, if you don't mind looking
like an orange traffic cone, great.
GirIfriends, I have the answer
to our dress problems.
(Bernadette:)Really?
Twelve years ago...
(Amy:)...my cousin Irene
and her entire family died...
...in a horrific carbon-monoxide accident
the night before her wedding.
- That's horrible.
- Yes and no.
(Amy:)All those bridesmaids dresses
remain unused...
(Amy:)...and available to us for free.
(Amy:)So it seems that cloud
of odorless, deadly gas...
(Amy:)...had a silver lining after all.
(Amy:)Check it out, still in the bags.
The gowns, not the bridesmaids.
(Bernadette:)I don't know. Dead people's dresses?
Yeah, and cap sleeves? Ehh...
Hmm. I was hoping
you wouldn't notice.
Irene was a slave to a good bargain
when it came to clothes...
(Amy:)...and, sadly, as it turned out,
space heaters.
(Sheldon:)Ladies, please.